# Maanas Sameer Nandan Muddam

748 Blake St Apt A, Indianapolis, IN (301) 712-7577 maanasm8@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/msnm https://github.com/maanasnandu

#### **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

Detail oriented and Creative Front-End web developer with 5+ years of experience, including 2+ years professionally. Expert in full-stack web applications. Former Front-end developer at Ozmo Inc., now a Systems Engineer at Infosys Inc. Known for reliability and teamwork.

#### **EDUCATION**

## B.S in Computer Science - Graduated on May 2022.

Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University Blacksburg, VA

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Webmaster - WebD-VT, Blacksburg, VA

Aug 2018 - September 2020

(Student organization at VT dedicated to hosting full-stack web development workshops and hackathon preps)

- Worked with a team of 4, used JS, HTML GitHub and Git Bash to clone and update webdvt.org web page.
- Conducted workshops to tutor JavaScript (Vanilla) and CSS.

# Associate Web Developer - Ozmo Inc., Blacksburg, VA

Aug 2020 - Dec 2020

(Mobile device support platform that helps mobile operators to solve device software issues)

- Collaborated with the squad lead and team to maintain workflow using JIRA boards, SVN and Airtable.
- Developed UX and Front-end for smartphone screens using JavaScript, Figma and XML.

# Systems Engineer - Infosys, Indianapolis, IN

July 2022 - present

(IT, digital services, and consulting company)

- Developed and maintained different web pages of Helix Hub platform using Angular (Front-end).
- Adhered to web design standards by synergizing with the UX team, utilizing Figma for page creation and workflow enhancement.
- Recipient of the Rise Insta award (2023) for contributions toward Helix Hub project and design-oriented development.
- Collaborated with diverse teams, adeptly navigating Agile methodologies, Scrum workflow, and JIRA boards. Leveraged Git Version Control System for efficient code management, ensuring project integrity and seamless collaboration across versions.

Collaborated with Tenant OPS on the Large Group Intake tool (LGIT), using Angular for front-end design while learning MySQL for database management and Azure.

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS & CERTIFICATIONS**

- HTML5/CSS3, JavaScript
- Figma, Adobe XD UX tools
- Angular (Framework), Node.js
- Java, MySQL (beginner)
- Azure Fundamentals (AZ-900) Cred ID: 89CFA3307CE60922, Cert #: 005F5A-143C98
- GitHub, Git VCS, JIRA